The orecle's words stand as a warning.
A prophecy
Spartans will fall.
All of Greece will fall.
And percian fire reduce athens to tinder.
for athene it's a pile of stone and wood and cloth and dust.
and as dust will vanish into the wind.
only athenians themselves exist.
And the fate of the world hangs on their every thinekle.
only the athenians exist.
and only ***** wooden ships can save them.
wooden ships...and tidal wave of heroes' blood.
Lienidus is my husband.
And he is your king.
Lienidus and brave three hundred are dead.
war is not their love
yet he lay down his life for them.
for the promise that greece holds.
It is our enemy who forged our freedom in fires of war.
It was our king Darius who came to take our land.
before this bitter war forced our children to become men.
ten years ago
this war began.
as all wars begin with the grivens.
Marothon.
The percian king -Darius
annoyed by notion of greek freedom.
This came to geece to bring us to heal.
He makes landfull field of marothon with in waving fools which have numbers of greek defendents three to one.
so what ****** hope athenian to do the unthinkable
They attack.
They attack the very percian ****** their ships and shaky legs a month at sea.
They attack they establish their warcam and supply their soldiers.
And who is the arcitech of this mass strategy?
A little known athenian soldier..
his men called him ''the mistic ****''.
He gives the percians the taste of athenian's shock combat.
all thoughts of glory are gone.
thousands dead ,
hundreds of them on their own
all for an idea,a free greece.
an athenian experiments called democrocy.
could this idea be worth it?worth all this sacrifice.
>
Themistocles would let the good King Darius decide
for through the
chaos,
a moment appeared
Themistocles would seize it.
a moment that would ring across a centuaries,
the moment that would raise him from a simple soldire
,
to the hieght of the athenian political power.
A moment that make Themistocles a legend.
yet even of the glory heat upon him.
Themistocles knew in his heart he'd made a mistake.
It was Darius son
, Xerxes
His eyes have the stinks of destiny about them.
Themistocles knew he should've killed that boy.
that gloriest mistake would forever haunt him.
as though it's the Themistocles who sent the ripper across the persian empire.
and set into motion forces that would bring fires to the heart of the greece.
for it's the good king in lay dying,
all his greatest genarals and advices sommond to his bed site
non greater than his finest neval commander.
Artemisia
her forsity bested only by her beauty.
her beauty match only by her devotion to her king.
Darius favored Artemisia amog his genarals know.
she has brought him the victory in the battelfield.
in her he had the perfect warrior .........
***** his son xerxes would never be.
my ..sweet..child..
My sweet..child..
Xerxes... do not repeat your fathers mistake
,
Only the god can defeat
them,
only the gods.
for  Seven days Xerxes mourned. paralyzed by grief,
, on the 8th day
Artemisia whispered seed of the maddness that would consume him.
Fathers words..
is a challenge
only the gods can defeat the Greeks.
You'll be a god king.
Artemisia gathered the priests,**** the every corner of the empire.
they wrapped the young king in simarian goose dipped in ancien potions.
and set him to one of the deserts.
to ***** with heat and thirst..
He stumbled upon a hermit cave.
i> Xerxes pased the vacant eyes.
an empty souls the hollowed creatures that dwelled in a dark coners
of every men's hearts.
and in that darkness
He surrended himself completely,
to power so evil and purves.
as he imerged no part of a human man war Xerxes survived
His eyes blaze like a ****
he was scriped,cleansed, glamorous and smooth.
Xerxes was reborn a god.
Artemisia trusted noone
so in the cover of knife.
palace was claimes all Xerxes allis.
all those he trusted
all those who raise him
all those he had once looked to for councel.
were quickly introdused to her raf.
and does the god king before his people
Artemisia watched her fluerest munipulation take shape.
= = a glory's sake
the vengence***
war!
war is coming to greece.
In the  **** of monster army over million stong.
It sould be little more than a
formality for the  themistocles,
The hero of marothon.
to finish what he began.
Please
we must appeal the Xerxes reasons.
coward.
La ยบ ity!
is a city of power.
Shut your own up.
silence!
This is a democracy, not a street fight
!
Persian attack will come from the both north and south.
- city *** should negotiate a truce.
- Yes, yes we must negotiate.
Negotiating will tear any..
give me one example of when that has ever profited to the nation/
My fellow country men,we can only judge
the future.
for what we had suffered in the past.
Now many of you here stood with me at the marothon
and for those of you who served and face the cut and thrust the battle,
you know how true peace is forged.
Do not be deceived.
Xerxes, son of Darius is a wolf at our door.
right here right now.
We must choose Do we stand fight for greece or not.
Akragas...
Corinth, Megara, Athens...
not even Sparta can marched the percian alone.
we must **** as one nation.
or we will perish clean onto our own self intrests.
send us the ships that we need to defend greece.
Themistocles would need more than our shitty ships.
He'll need our children to join the fight.
- What of Sparta?
- Send every ship that we have,
to the north coast of Evia.
I'll go and seek the help.
in the great Sparta...
Still no word from the messenger you sent to Sparta.
King Leonidas may have been insulted by your generous offer.
perhaps we need to march sparta myself and burn into the ground.
Remember...when a king is loveed*****
a much can be accomplished.
He will be forced to resist my divine power.
Athens is attempting to assemble a coalition.
It will be nothing more than bunch work of a ships.
...
how we remind ******  that we have not forgotten.
rest the horses.it's best i go alone.
Spartans do not get along well with us.
- Sparta...
- Themistocles...
what brings you to the sparta?
I've come to see Leonidas to warn him Persian are in the march
.
well you are too late.
Persian massenger already presented these terms to the Leonidas.
A symbolic offer to the land and water.
Spartan,know this and know this well.
It ain't spata's finest moments.
the greatest fullfilment that all he holds dear,
is that moment.
lies dead on the battlefield,
victorious.
now.who's willing to die at our king side?
Themistocles...
you've come a long way to stroke your cock to watch real men
train.
queen Gogra.shouldn't you be traing them to live at their king side?
A new age is downing over.
that sounds like a treat.
- No. ..
an opertunity to join over the rest free greeks to stand against the *****.
Unless of cause you and Leonidas had already made a deal with Xerxes.
exept Xerxes's messenger,but he was rude without respect.
he didn't notice same treats do not work here.
This is the birthplace of world's greatest warriors
.
the men who's king would stand and fight for any one of them.
exept he's massengerdid not understand that this is no typical Greek city state.
This is Sparta.
so it was clear to the massenger,there would be no spartans on this mission.
It was clear.Even now Leonidas
has encouncel with oracle over his battle plan.
Festival of the carne stands in our way.
Surely oracle will see we must fight.
When the timing is perfect.
I am commanding *** of ships representing
united greece.
I want sparta to join me.
Give me your ship
Gorgo and I will make sure that Xerxes
wishes he would never crosses the edge again.
You will receive no Spartan ship.
We are not interested in united greece.
That is your dream, Themistocles,
not ours.
all i concered with preservation of sparta.
My guard will see you out.
It's funny that you mock freedom here in your ******
yet freedom inher wisdom.
has chosen you to defend her.
My Queen...
Will Sparta join our fight?
Apparantly Persian has offered Sparta
something they can not refuse.
And what?
A beautiful death.
They say you are the bravest among captains.
They say you're a whore
from the eastern seas.
not the smartest.
Your commander is a greek just like me.
, you Persian men,
takes your orders from a  Greek woman.
yes'my brother.i am greek by birth.
And i have Greek blood running through my veins.
But my heart...
is Persian.
Within hours....
Greek fleet will be shut.
What about master?and mush feared sparta?
There is nothing to fear.
Only King Leonidas and his personal guards of 300.
march to fight.
look...
you...
Do you agree?
Many of will perish...
your Confidence leaves me with a strong impression.
It's a curious thing for a single ship guard,to not learn his eyes when question by me.
for the eyes, and when I asked him something.
******* lack of discipline.
A man's hands do not lie.
they can reveal every  imperfections and flaws of his character.
You see, your hands are not rough enough to work
to***of the ship.
I know every single man beneath my lash.
you explain to me.
how i know you?
Excuse me Commander.
let me introduce myself.
ceise the spy!
coward.
Storm is upon us.
It's just some bad greek whether.
Themistocles
-come.
-
Calisto - we are spoken here would not be repeated.
Anywhere.
My son has not earn the right to sit at the table of combat of veterens,
but you can trust him.
very well.
- Tell me.
- A greek women commands all the xerxes ships to the south.
Artemisia, I know of her.
Artemisia is merderous by trade which whose skills at sea.
she has thirst for vengeance.
her entire family was murdered by a scodd of greek ****.
I have heard all the stories.
The story goes that raped and murdered her family.
When they turned their attention towards her...
After years being kept above in greek slave ship.
she was discard and left for dead.
where she found near dead by percian himself.
Artemisia  vowed  that day to return to greece.
only when she could watch it burn.
shewas fed,clothed and trained by the finest warriors
of Persian empire.
no match could be found for her skills and gift for the sword.
great King Darius was impressed by her commitment.
and she quickly grows
next commander.
She has sold her soul to the death himself.
some could say i sold mine to greece.
- What do you think?
- ?
Guess, You are the future of this country.
I am ready to fight.
I like him.
we will need every last man.
He's still just a boy.
-a much younger had defended our country, father.
- Enough!
You are a dreamer who
speak of this no more.
Themistocles,
I said your plan in motion
and my land force will be assemble by the secondary.
you won't be needed.
I can assure you of that.
now there is a bad news.
Leonidas has marched north to the hot gates.
Bad news?
The Spartans on the hot gates
our victory is assured.
If the army will with him.
Between Oracle and ,carny
Leonidas has marched with 300 men
So the only thing standing between  Athens and total elimination
is Leonidas and 300 Spartans
establish a oder around the volunteers.
Good.
Allow them time to teach them some of their strategies.
Just keep them well fed ...
and sober.
- Anything else?
- It would not hurt if they swim to shore.
I'll be damned!
- Damn!
- Does your father  know that  you're here?
No, sir.
- And a shield and sword?
- My grandfathers'.
My mother entrusted them to me morning.
- she gave her blessing?
- Yes, sir.
it's a sharp blade...
Your father is preparing a surprise raide in tomorrow.
I choose to fight here, now.
Come aboad my ship and it is where you fight.
Yes, sir.
We just own a 50 ships.
Persian Forces are devoted nonthethan thousands.
ships appear hardly see worthy.
nothing like the monstrous ships in the persian fleet.
Then we have the advantage.
Speed and maneuverability.
Rest this city stakes in any of them handfull to a single ship,of cause happens.
supply the balance.
We have a report that a small  avance force of percian ships are taken refuge from a storm just across the straight.
With the breaks,we can hit them at dawn.
- Early Greek victory.
- The gods has given us an opertuanity.
to wound the pesian and extract them greek moral.
attempting distraction.
We'll stick to the battle plan.
Today at sundown we'll sail out to meet to the main pecian fleet.
We'll attack them in the open water with no short to narrow the battle.
Attack a force over a thosand ships
with armfull of force is suiside.
Such is my plan.
Look at their exuse for navy.
Their ships are little treats.
I need a second in command , Ephialtes.
And whoever proves their exelence,will own place beside me.
General Bandari has offered to lead the first attack.
- Commander?
- I let you lead our first offense.
What guarantee do I have that you will bring me a quick victory
?
-My word and my life.
- Good.
- My rules of engagement?
- humiliate the Greeks and lay waste to their tiny ships.
They will be dead to the last man.
My brothers, steady your hearts,
and look deep into your soul.
we will all be ***  tested this day.
if we're in the heat of battle
You need a reason to fight on.
idea...which you will give up all that you'll ever have.
You need only to look at the man fights at your side.
This is the **** of battle.
This is the brotherhood of men and arms.
An unbreakable bond made stronger by the cruisifer of the combat.
You never will be close with all those who shared your blood with.
There is no nobler cause that the fight for those
who lay down and given their life for you.
You fight strong today.
you fight for your brothers.
Fight for your families.
Most of all you fught for greece.
THere is only one thing to make sure when the fighting starts.
What's that?
Do not get killed on the first day.
That goes for the rest of you.
Persian ships are strong in the front.
but they are weak in the middle.
we attack them there.
Now!
Round Up!
Reverse!
Now!
Go through them.
Enemy's tactics are created.
Defensife circle is no front on .....*
-we're loosing.
- No, you are loosing.
Pull back.
Let them have this day.
I'm bored with your failures
Bandari.
I will not let this wound slow me.
Somehow, I believe you.
My blade will be sharp and ready by the morning.
Good.
Tomorrow you will fight along side with your father.
- Not bad for bunch of farmers.
- And poets and sculptors.
Who would've known group of untrained men do so well
against such a considarable ****
WE are gonna need all of our stength tomorrow's fight.
How long do you think we can hold?
If my plan is to work...
Long enough for spatans to unite the greece.
Who shall share their wine with me?
- Report!
- we're still carrying the losses.
But you must understand that
it is extremly difficult
live in the sea and......
Report?
75 ships lost.
30 ships need be repaired.
20 good return a few weeks work in a safe harbour.
the commander of the greek force named Teotocles.
Yes, He is an athenian genaral.
He is Rumored to lose the arrow that fell the great
king Darius himself.
This Themistocles has shown himself quiet brilliant in battle.
Which is more I can say for any of you.
.
Do you gentlemen find my command reasonable?
Is it too much to ask for victory?
Your dissapointment in yesterday's losses is warrented.
My dissapointment?
My dissapointment is not with my losses.
A *** number of damaged ships and dead slavesmeans nothing to me.
No.
My dissapontment...
Is in these men.
for stand among ten thousand.
I am alone.
I longed for a soul who stands by my side
I can trust.
Tell me General Kashani,
Are you that man?
You will taste your victory by the day's end.
I'll make certain of it.
I hope so.
Advance!
Now!
Got any sight of them?
- The Greeks are retreated.
- He's got it right where he want it.
General Kashani is a fine stactition....
Speaking of Themistocles.
Rocks!
Stop!
Raise your self.
- What are you doing here?
-A man's responsibility is
protect his family and his nation.
- Who told you this?
- My father.
you see how euphemistically is
frustration with the grandeur?
Why is it so much to ask a victory?
- How can i make a...
- Silence.
you will carry a massage for me.
Now they will fear us!
Now they will fear the Greeks!
He's right!
fear the Greek fighting men.
fear his sword and his shield.
Fear his love for mother greece.
,
but most of all...
fear his freedom.
Do not get angry with the boy.
- I took him under my command.
- Anger is somthing I reserved from  my enemies.
Themistocles!
Artemisia ship is being anchored to neutral waters.
- she's like to  meet with Themistocles.
- How can you gurantee his safe return?
Well,boy/
THe only honor for her now will be watching you crush
and broken fleet sink in to the bottom Aegean.
She will be able to recognize you
nailed to the master ship with her sword.
as you descent in to the waterly grave.
Why didn't you say that in begining?
Welcome to my ***** ship.
We are honored by your presence.
******** you.quiet impressive.
Kind ones...
Now come Themistocles,
We must
discuss.
Do you believe the Greeks are descendants from the gods?
I have heard something.
And what of you?still a god in new**
I say there's a spoken the
divine in you.
Now who's using kind words.
My men used to say it was you slaged the good king Darius at Marothon.
Many heroic deeds occured that day.
It was 10 years ago.
Facts of  battle are
often reimeged.
This deed you would remember.
I will do what i must to defend greece.
And I'll do what I must to defeat her.
For every greek get killed you must kill a thousand percians.
.
For every ship I sink
you must sink a hundred.
Against **** weeks,months
If maybe.
My numbers will defeat you.
And I'll take your precious boats with my sword and i'll take your greek freedom.
you asking me to ne
gotiate a surrender?
No. ..
I offer you a chance to avoid such a misery and join me.
I may have a need of a commander such
as you.
Look at the
defense.
A handfull of****
Leonidas and with Spartans.
It is insulting to the mightiest empire  the world has ever seen.
I didn't blam you
, Themistocles.
You fought as if the blood of posiden himself causing through your veins.
I blame Greece.
Bureaucracy and political protecting *******
and sending you here to die.
And yet he still fights.
So there must be.....what?
A family back who holds nothing but compells you to..
fight with such a passion..
Actually I had no time for family.
I've spent my entire life with my one true love
.
the Greek Fleet...an amount  passion
readying it
for you.
Now that it brings me pleasure the s ought of you hiving away from me
seeking family and love
A promise that deeper ****
The Ecstasy of you in flesh
Death and knives...
and rage....and sweat of mucsle.
of
pure joy
And deepest sorrow.
Dine with me tonight and be born with me in morning..
sword into the hearts of our enemy
you fight for freedom,
I offer freedom
without consequences or responsibilities
Join me.
And my side.
breath each breath with me as  it will be your
last breath.
Join me.
N
o.
You are no god,you are just a man.
Be quick with your sword.
You'll not have your death tonight.
Guards!
Remove this filth from my ship.
Well, what have you learned?
Can Artemisia be beat?
The next time  that we face her.she's going to bring war of hell wiyh her.
Send in my personal guards.
- Pull back
- Retreat!
Retreat!
Themistocles, in the water!
Archers.ark that now.
Archers
on the deck now!
Fast!
Fire......
fight on, boy!
fight on.
Aim for the man on top.
aim for him.
Abandon ship!
The dead have no guilt.
No responsibility
Themistocles watched bodies of his men turned The Aegean red with blood.
Were they sacrificed with his ego?
Or to e*** the guilt of long ago mistake at Marathon.
How many men would have been
saved  if Themistocles had kiledl that boy.
Not even his own soul can be sure.
And you my friend,we fight
*****
together.
Listen to me, Themistocles,
You'll have to fight twice as much as strength in the morning.
- we'll fight shoulder to shoulder.
- No, my son.
You carry on for both of us.
What did he say?
I will tell you in time, boy.
Quiet now.
God be with your father's spirit.
How many times do you think we'll repeat such a tragedy?
As many as times we must.
We are turning young men in to memories.
Do you think I enjoy this?
Witnessing my friend's last breath.
Every widow that has made by my dicision.
every child who'll  grow up without a father
.
They are my choices.
This is the burden of my command.
How easy is it to silence strong and self destruct.
Let my army witness the great warriors of sparta.
.
March them past these corpses.
Let them see
cost dared to challenge the god-king.
King Leonidas and his brave 300
The finest Greece has to offer.
There will be no saviors to rise up and f***** us.
Nothing will stop the march of my empire.
your majesty...
You take the this dead king's sword to Athens.
Let them know that I am coming next for them.
Let them know.....Athens, their jewel of the city.
Will disappear from the history.
Themistocles!
I bring word from
Thermopylae.
Leonidas was betrayed by a honk back.
Spartans has been slaughtered.
Hotgates are falling
.
Such a sacrifice
!
Now Greece has
a martyr.
Daxos, take this message from the hotgates.
to every city,to village and to every country men.
- hear your words.
- but they are dead,all of them.
Sparta's sacrifice is what's
unite us.
Now, go!
move all of  our shipa and men back to the safty and.....
- And you? I will take  Daxos's massage to  Athens.
i was told honkback
Fire Doors Atul hair bump.
but he sold out his
country.
from his back and replace it with persian gold.
What is your name, traitor?
Ephialtes of
Thrace.
I shall wet this noble blade with your blood.
you would be right to do so.
there is little beauty about me .
and there is a little beauty in what i have done.
Say what you must.
I beg of you.
and all the Athenians.
The God King will burn this city to the ground.
quiet yourself.
Leonidas and the Spartans' great sacrifice.
was no defeat.
It was a beautiful victory,
This simple act of ****
Will allow us to rally each of our city states
and unite Greece.For one purpose.
against one enemy.
And you,you take this message to your God King,
We will take whatever ships we have left
And finish this in
bay of Salamis.
- But there will be death and destruction?
- Yes
There will be.
Themistocles.
I'm here to speak to the queen.
I warn you, Athenian,
you may not recieve a worm wecome.
May I offer my deepest sympathies.
We can not change what has happened to Leonidas.
But his sacrifice will not be forgotten.
Do not lecture me of sacrifice and
be quick with your words,Athenian.
I request of you the entire spartan navy.
Every man,every ship that you can spare.
Have i not given enough for your dream of united Greece.
Shall i put sword in hands of my son.
Our children?
Would that please you?
have I not given enough for your ambitions,
Themistocles?
A King, husbands, fathers, brothers.
Sparta will give no more.
This belongs with you.
Avenge him!
Oracle's words stood as a warning.
All of Greece will fall.
AS persian fire reduces The Athenes to thinder.
For Athenes ith's a pile of stone and wood and cloth and dust.
As dust would vanish into the wind.
Only the Athenian themselves exist.
And the fathe of the world hangs on their every syllable.
Only the Athenians exist.
and only ***
wooden ships can save them.
Wooden Ships...
And the tidal waves of heroes'
blood.
The Greeks would be fools to stand against us.
Leonidas and Sparta is no match for the will of the God's.
Themistocles  is worth it.
Worthless coward,Now, this pathetic navy *******
that wothless coward has stood up my side wounded up the world at you feet.
My king...your Humble servent.
brings you news.
The Greek fleets are defendless.
In bay of salamis,
you need only to finish them.
Who cammands their forces?
Themistocles of Athens.
Themistocles is dead.
He's alive.
I have seen him myself..
Ready my troops and ***.
We'll attack at once.
Where is them?
would have a send a probin force to  confirm it is not a trap.
you'd dare advise me on *** of war?
I am the God-king.
I am the one who ***** over Leonidas.
I am the one who laid waste of shore piece of athens.
I am your king.
killing Leonidas and his men only made them
martyrs.
But when you erased Athens,
you set fire to the only thing that value in this country.
We will attack the greeks with my entire navy.
Artemisia, enough!
Do not forget who put the crown on your childish head, My King.
Now sit on your golden throne,
watch this battle from the safety I provide you.
We're in the distance,
we'd miss the destruction of Athens.
Along real face of the monster that cast a shadow across our land.
I had prayed that the Spartans would come to
led a hand in this morning.
perhaps they feel they've given enough.
You've failed us all.
This is your fault, Themistocles.
without  Spartan we are just farmhands.
we should've
negotiated with the Persians whenhe had the chance.
you are all right.
Yes, we are down to a handful of boats.
and yes we are just farmhands.
we are tradesmen.
we are boys.
turned to men through the sacrifice.
forge of combat.
I played a dangerous game
and i lost.
if you choose to turn your back on me.
on your country.
I will not judge you.
you are free to leave.
your still free men.
very well.
Then let us put our shoulder to work.
and free those ships from the busam of greece.
Today is a privilege to call our own
A story that would be told for a thousand yeas.
let our final stand be recorded to the history.
let it be shown that we chose to die on our feet.
rather than live on your knees.
There is only one thing you need to know today.
not to get killed
No.
your father's Last words.
He told me  you have to earn the right to sit at the table.
Well my brother, no more tactics and tricks
.
This will be the last battle that we share.
we were full next to one another for as long as I can remember.
nothing will please me more than the rest this sword.
- The preparation that i require...
- are below deck.
Good.
ARe you sure you want to commit everything?
-yes
Without Aretemisia's command pesian navy will be nothing.
- We will never be able to reach her.
- I'll reach her.
And put an end to this.
There will be no room for a retreat.
I know.
Today the last GReek ships will be destroyed.
show them no mercy!
Give them no quarter
!
Today we will dance above the backs of dead greeks.
Today we deliver submission.
Today, I wanna feel Themistocles troat beneath my boots.
Men! brace  yourselves.
ATTACK....
feel your glory!
I'm not here as a witness,
Now!
Let them send their souls straight to hell.
We all **** our consequences and responsibilities.
Are you accepting my offer?
My answer is still no.
You fight much harder than you fuck.
\
Surrender to me or meet your death.
Who do you fight, if not for me?
No one could chalenge your skill.
I would rather die free man than as a slave.
Even was the chains attached to you.
It begins as a whisper,a promise.
It moves through her hair as gently as a lover's hand.
That breeze that promise became a wind.
A wind was blown across Greece carrying a massage told again and again
of our lady freedom.
How wise she was to charge Leonidas
to lay all at her feet.
A wind that my brothers have
sacrificed
.
A wind of freedom.
A wind of justise.
A wind of vengeance.
You're being surrounded.All of Greece has united against you.
Delphi, Thebes, Olympus,
Arcadia and Sparta.
If death comes for me today,I am ready.
I could lower my sword.
There is still time for you to ready a launch and escape.
It would be a poor choice,to force my hand into action.
Now all your ships disengage and surronded to me.
surronder?
SYNCED AND CORRECTED BY THIWABKA AT SUBSCENE.COM